Feed the Gu team
Gu 팀에게 먹이주기
You just submitted your order report
방금 주문 보고서를 제출했습니다.
Please help me modify it
수정하도록 도와주세요
The lord of Saiyuan City is named Li Yi
사이위안 성주의 이름은 리이(Li Yi)입니다.
There are also people from Yin Tianhong
인텐홍(Yin Tianhong) 출신도 있습니다.
Li Yi is about thirty-five years old
리 이의 나이는 서른다섯 살 정도다.
Yin Tianhong is about twenty-seven years old
Yin Tianhong은 약 27세입니다.
An Qiu just had sex with me.
An Qiu는 방금 나와 섹스를 했습니다.
chew
씹다
Thanks
감사해요
I didn't expect it
나는 그것을 기대하지 않았다
lack of experience
경험의 부족
Let's go eat first
먼저 먹으러 가자
I think
제 생각에는
Li Yi must make money to make ends meet.
Li Yi는 생계를 유지하려면 돈을 벌어야 합니다.
he looks tall and tall
그 사람 키가 크고 커 보여요
He will definitely choose some highly mobile employees
그는 확실히 이동성이 뛰어난 직원을 선택할 것입니다
But authentication
하지만 인증
This is not a strict assignment
이것은 엄격한 임무가 아니다
And this job
그리고 이 직업은
Not particularly clear
특별히 명확하지 않음
Do you think it's possible for him?
그 사람에게 그게 가능하다고 생각하세요?
I'm looking for temporary work on a construction site
건설현장에서 임시직을 구하고 있습니다
perhaps
아마도
A construction site with people coming and going
사람들이 오가는 공사장
I don't particularly care who is who.
나는 누가 누구인지 특별히 신경 쓰지 않습니다.
I will ask my friends to find out
친구들한테 물어봐야겠어요
friend
친구
In fact, he is a middleman
사실 그는 중개인이다.
People who specialize in helping illegal residents
불법체류자 도움을 전문으로 하는 사람들
I'm looking for temporary employment
임시직을 찾고 있어요
I didn't expect you to be so popular.
당신이 그렇게 인기가 많을 줄은 몰랐어요.
I often see you walking alone
혼자 걷는 걸 자주 보는데
Many friends
많은 친구들
Agent sent message
상담원이 메시지를 보냈습니다.
Sure enough, Li Yi called him.
과연 리이가 그에게 전화를 걸었다.
mark with stars
별표로 표시하다
This is the place where Li Yi once stayed
이곳은 Li Yi가 한때 머물렀던 곳입니다.
Li Yi has always been cautious
리이는 늘 조심스러웠다
The changing workplace
변화하는 직장
He is at the construction site
그는 건설현장에 있다
The maximum stay is only one month
최대 체류 기간은 한 달입니다.
Check out these websites
다음 웹사이트를 확인해 보세요.
There are construction sites everywhere in the southeast, northwest and northwest
남동쪽, 북서쪽, 북서쪽 곳곳에 건설현장이 있습니다
no rules to follow
따라야 할 규칙이 없습니다
He's scared we'll find him
그 사람은 우리가 그를 찾을까봐 겁이 나
perhaps
아마도
He is not afraid of us
그 사람은 우리를 두려워하지 않아요
But I'm afraid of killer robots
하지만 킬러로봇은 무서워요
Where was Li Yi last seen?
Li Yi가 마지막으로 목격된 곳은 어디입니까?
Agent proposes an idea
상담원이 아이디어를 제안함
Li Yi once asked about this shipping company
Li Yi는 한때 이 운송 회사에 대해 물었습니다.
Are they all loaded into the car?
모두 차에 실렸나요?
All installed
모두 설치됨
All right
괜찮은
Hello boss
안녕하세요 사장님
Our eyes are bright
우리 눈은 밝아
Want to investigate you?
당신을 조사하고 싶나요?
About robots
로봇에 대하여
welcome
환영
Do you know Li Yi?
리이(Li Yi)를 아시나요?
Li Yi
리 이
correct
옳은
we know each other
우리는 서로를 알아
He has been working here for three months
그는 여기서 3개월 동안 일해왔습니다
But I have resigned now
하지만 지금은 사임했어요
How about everyone else?
다른 사람들은 어떻습니까?
others
다른 사람
I feel good
나는 기분이 좋다
The car runs very well
차는 아주 잘 달린다
I've been working here for three months
나는 여기서 3개월 동안 일했어요
Don't say it's a small cut or scrape.
작은 상처나 긁힌 자국이라고 말하지 마십시오.
Not even a violation
위반도 아니고
when he left
그가 떠났을 때
I'm totally hesitant to break up with him
나는 그 사람과 헤어지는 것을 완전히 망설이고 있다
Brother Peng
펭 형제
came back
돌아왔다
This is the inspection sheet
점검표 입니다
All right
괜찮은
It has been sent to three places
세 곳으로 보냈어요
Well, thank you for your hard work. Did he say why he left?
글쎄요, 수고해주셔서 감사합니다. 그가 떠난 이유를 말했나요?
Why did you leave?
왜 떠났어?
This is not said
이것은 말하지 않았다
This is his personal problem
이건 그 사람 개인적인 문제야.
It's not my place to ask too many questions.
너무 많은 질문을 하는 것은 제가 할 일이 아닙니다.
Do you still have his contact information?
아직도 그 사람 연락처를 갖고 있나요?
have
가지다
this
이것
But I dialed this number
그런데 이 번호로 전화를 걸었어요
The number is empty
번호가 비어 있습니다.
Thanks
감사해요
Thank you, I'll be busy first.
고마워요. 먼저 바쁠게요.
welcome
환영
I want one
내가 하나를 원하는
smaller birthday cake
작은 생일 케이크
I asked
나는 물었다
Pengcheng Freight has two more drivers
Pengcheng Freight에는 운전자가 두 명 더 있습니다
About Li Yi
리이(Li Yi) 소개
What they said is basically the same as what Huang Shipeng said.
그들이 말한 내용은 기본적으로 Huang Shipeng이 말한 것과 동일합니다.
In addition, the mobile phone number provided by Huang Shiping
또한, 황시핑(Huang Shiping)이 제공한 휴대폰 번호
It was canceled last month
지난달에 취소됐어요
It seems that Li Yi has no intention of contacting anyone.
리이는 누구에게도 연락할 생각이 없는 것 같다.
I just feel weird
그냥 기분이 이상해
Li Yi works at a construction site.
Li Yi는 건설 현장에서 일합니다.
Why did you come to Huang Shiping?
왜 황십평에 오셨나요?
It took three months
3개월 걸렸어요
perhaps
아마도
Compared to other jobs, driver
다른 직업에 비해 운전수는
safer
더 안전한
Huang Shiping
황 시핑
He's such a good boss
정말 좋은 상사예요
Feed the Gu team
Gu 팀에게 먹이주기
Hello, Ms. Cheng
안녕하세요, 쳉 씨
Huang Shiping case
황시핑 사건
It seems to have something to do with Android
안드로이드와 관련이 있는 것 같습니다.
I have sent you the information
정보를 보내드렸습니다
OK, thanks
알았어 고마워
What's wrong
뭐가 문제 야
Sent to me by the Gu team
구팀에서 나한테 보냈어
Huang Shiping family information
황시핑 가족 정보
There must be something wrong
뭔가 문제가 있는 게 틀림없어
No wonder Li Yi stayed at Pengcheng Freight for so long
Li Yi가 Pengcheng Freight에 오랫동안 머물렀던 것도 당연합니다.
Maybe there is something similar here
아마 여기도 비슷한 게 있을 것 같아
look at this
이거 봐요
This was twelve years ago
이건 12년 전이야
Prescription records of Huang Shiping and Li Han’s wife
황십핑(Huang Shiping)과 리한(Li Han) 부인의 처방 기록
Huang Shiping’s wife is probably infertile
황십핑 아내 불임 가능성 높아
Happy birthday
생일 축하해요
silver
은
Conger, are you okay?
콘저, 괜찮아?
Does my father scare you?
우리 아빠가 널 무서워하니?
Dad, I was kidding you.
아빠, 농담했어요.
You scared me to death
당신은 나를 겁에 질려 죽게 만들었습니다.
I saw you in the mirror a long time ago
오래전에 거울에서 너를 봤어
don't do this again
다시는 이러지 마세요
exhibit
전시하다
Happy birthday
생일 축하해요
Where is the cake?
케이크는 어디에 있나요?
eat first
먼저 먹어라
Eating cake again
케이크 또 먹고
OK
좋아요
Happy birthday
생일 축하해요
make a wish
소원을 말해봐
This is great, this is great
이거 대단해, ​​이거 대단해
what do you want?
당신은 무엇을 원하세요?
I hope I can be with my father forever
나는 아버지와 영원히 함께 할 수 있기를 바랍니다
This is really my dad’s little cotton-padded jacket.
이건 정말 우리 아빠의 작은 솜 패딩 재킷이에요.
take it with you
그것을 가지고 가세요
Let's cut the cake
케이크를 자르자
Do you love daddy?
아빠를 사랑해요?
I bought you this cake
내가 이 케이크를 사줬어
like
좋다
Choose your favorite strawberry flavor.
좋아하는 딸기 맛을 선택하세요.
right for anyone
누구에게나 딱
I want to go home
집에 가고 싶어
OK
좋아요
Ok, see you tomorrow
그래 내일 보자
goodbye
안녕히 가세요
Who is this?
누구세요?
a bright eyed person
눈이 밝은 사람
come to me today
오늘 나한테 와
I learned about Li Yi’s situation
리이의 상황을 알게 됐어요
He also said
그는 또한 말했다
I'll go home tomorrow
내일 집에 갈게요
What is he doing in our house?
그 사람이 우리 집에서 뭐 하고 있는 걸까요?
Will Cong'er not be interrogated?
Cong'er는 심문을받지 않습니까?
perhaps
아마도
call her
그녀에게 전화해
That's what I'm worried about too
그게 나도 걱정이야
Mom and Dad, come and cut the cake.
엄마, 아빠, 와서 케이크를 자르세요.
exist
존재하다
Cut the cake Cut the cake
케이크를 잘라 케이크를 잘라
Come, come, come
오세요, 오세요, 오세요
Lycangill
라이칸길
Do you know this sentence?
이 문장을 아시나요?
Of course I know him
물론 난 그 사람을 알아요
It has been six years since Huang Xiping moved here
황시핑이 이곳으로 이사온 지 6년이 지났습니다.
more than six years
6년 이상
when the couple first moved here
부부가 처음 이곳으로 이사왔을 때
I still have some impressions
아직도 인상이 좀 남았어
people are very polite
사람들은 매우 예의바르다
Take it, take it, take it
가져가, 가져가, 가져가
I will definitely bother you in the future.
앞으로는 꼭 귀찮게 할게요.
How much time is needed?
얼마나 많은 시간이 필요합니까?
just the two of us
단지 우리의 두
almost
거의
Then hurry up
그럼 서둘러
Thank you so much
매우 감사합니다
Thanks
감사해요
Hold on
기다리다
Where is his daughter?
그의 딸은 어디에 있나요?
girl
소녀
It may have been moved here later.
나중에 여기로 옮겨졌을 수도 있어요.
Anyway, when you sign up
아무튼 가입하면
There were only two of them there
그 곳에는 두 사람밖에 없었어요
Since they moved here?
그들이 여기로 이사한 이후로요?
we can always meet
우리는 언제나 만날 수 있어요
Looks like it did when I first moved here
처음 여기로 이사왔을 때도 그랬던 것 같아요
I've never seen her take care of a child
나는 그녀가 아이를 돌보는 것을 본 적이 없다
Only one time
한번만
we are adults
우리는 어른이다
Playing there with a bunch of kids
그곳에서 아이들과 함께 놀아요
She happened to be there too
마침 그녀도 거기 있었어
See how much you love children
당신이 아이들을 얼마나 사랑하는지보십시오
Let's ask her
그녀에게 물어보자
you love children very much
당신은 아이들을 매우 사랑합니다
She gave birth soon after
그녀는 곧 출산을 했고
Yeah, guess what she said
응, 그 사람이 뭐라고 했는지 맞춰봐
i have children
나에겐 아이가 있어요
You said you have children
아이가 있다고 하셨어요
Why do you always stare at other people's children?
왜 남의 자식만 쳐다보나요?
Don't play with your children
아이들과 놀지 마세요
Isn't this something wrong with your brain?
이건 뇌에 문제가 있는 것 아닌가요?
Of course, it is also possible that at that time
물론 그 당시에도 그럴 가능성이 있다.
Child follows his grandparents
아이는 조부모를 따른다
I don't live with them
나는 그들과 함께 살지 않는다
Which
어느
They wouldn’t know it was me who said that, would they?
그 사람들은 내가 그런 말을 했다는 걸 몰랐을 텐데요, 그렇죠?
will not
~하지 않을 것이다
Then you still have an impression
그럼 아직도 인상이 남아있어
When did they happen?
언제 그런 일이 일어났나요?
Did you bring Cong'er?
콩아를 ​​데려왔나요?
Maybe they moved here
아마 여기로 이사했을지도 몰라
About half a year
반년 정도
When was this taken?
이건 언제 찍은 거야?
This is my daughter's summer vacation
이번이 우리 딸의 여름방학이에요
Let's hang out and shoot
놀고 쏘자
What about this one?
이건 어때?
it seems
것 같다
this is very good
이건 아주 좋아요
That was when my daughter was six or seven years old
그때가 내 딸이 예닐곱 살이었을 때였어.
Your daughter is so cute
딸이 너무 귀여워요
Are there any photos of her when she was younger?
그녀의 어렸을 때 사진이 있나요?
there is nothing
아무것도 없다
Where are my childhood photo albums?
내 어린 시절 사진 앨범은 어디에 있나요?
Lost it when moving
이사하면서 잃어버렸어요
Mobile version
모바일 버전
There's always a computer version, right?
항상 컴퓨터 버전이 있죠?
I'm really sorry
정말 미안해요
two two two two
둘 둘 둘 둘
I don't understand a little
조금 이해가 안 돼요
This is what it looks like
이것이 바로 그 모습이다
I want to ask
나는 묻고 싶다
photo of my daughter
내 딸의 사진
And Li Yi’s disappearance
그리고 리이의 실종
Is there any connection?
어떤 연관성이 있나요?
Don't worry
괜찮아요
We're just asking
우리는 단지 묻는 것뿐입니다.
That's it
그게 다야
If nothing else
다른 것이 없다면
I still have a lot of work to do today
오늘도 아직 할 일이 많아요
What if Li Yi calls me?
리이가 나한테 전화하면 어떡하지?
my first time
나의 처음
Reporting to you is Mr. Huang
보고하는 사람은 Mr. Huang입니다.
I'll just say this
이 말만 할게
What about Li Yi this time?
이번에는 리이(Li Yi)가 어떻습니까?
I have one more thing I want to confirm with you
한 가지 더 확인하고 싶은 게 있어요
Can you tell me
나에게 말해줄 수 있나요?
Where did your daughter live until she was seven?
당신의 딸은 일곱 살이 될 때까지 어디에서 살았나요?
two
둘
Which
어느
Are you two people?
두 사람입니까?
Is there any misunderstanding?
오해가 있나요?
You doubt my daughter
내 딸을 의심하는구나
Is it a robot?
로봇인가요?
no
아니요
We are still investigating
우리는 아직 조사 중입니다
you must have made a mistake
너 실수한 게 틀림없어
Yes, yes, this is impossible
응, 응, 이건 불가능해
Then why your daughter?
그럼 딸은 왜요?
That's it, Mr. Huang, Mrs. Huang
바로 그거예요, 황 씨, 황 씨
We can't find it in the database
데이터베이스에서 찾을 수 없습니다
Huang Cong'er's life record before he was seven years old
황충아가 일곱 살이 되기 전의 인생 기록
Can you explain it?
설명해주실 수 있나요?
Then I won’t hide it from you.
그러면 나는 그것을 당신에게 숨기지 않을 것입니다.
my daughter
내 딸
She was kidnapped as a child
그녀는 어렸을 때 납치당했어요
kidnapping
유괴
correct
옳은
How old were you then?
그때 몇 살이었나요?
three years old
세 살
Her mother took her shopping
그녀의 어머니는 쇼핑을 데리고 갔다
careless
경솔한
waste
쓰레기
When did you get it back?
언제 다시 돌려받았나요?
when i was six years old
내가 여섯 살이었을 때
How to recover?
회복하는 방법?
Someone saw her on the street
누군가가 길에서 그녀를 봤어
The police saved her
경찰이 그녀를 구해줬어요
So before you find Cong'er
그러니 Cong'er를 찾기 전에
I have moved
이사했어요
so you are not afraid
그러니 너는 두려워하지 않는다
What if Conger comes back alone?
붕어가 혼자 돌아오면 어쩌지?
Can not find you?
너를 찾을 수 없다?
Which
어느
Actually that's it
사실 그게 다야
ship for me
나를 위해 배송
The child was missing at that time
그 때 그 아이가 실종됐어요
I'm in a state of ecstasy
나는 황홀경에 빠졌어
Serious illness
심각한 병
Doctors suggest we change our living environment
의사들은 생활 환경을 바꾸라고 제안합니다
We just moved
우리 방금 이사했어요
We never stop looking for babies
우리는 아기를 찾는 것을 멈추지 않습니다
Yeah
응
Fortunately, I finally found it
다행히 드디어 찾았어요
Yes
예
Then you still remember
그럼 아직도 기억나?
What kind of police is that?
그게 무슨 경찰이냐?
How to deal with this situation?
이 상황을 어떻게 처리해야 할까요?
Last name is
성은
Is that so, officer?
그렇죠, 경관님?
Yes
예
Is there any contact information?
연락처가 있나요?
Yes I have
네, 있어요
this
이것
we need to check
우리는 확인해야 해
no problem
괜찮아요
Can I talk to Cong'er alone?
Cong'er와 단둘이 대화할 수 있나요?
Isn't that appropriate?
적절하지 않나요?
The child is still young
아이가 아직 어려서
I'm afraid of making her unhappy again
나는 그녀를 다시 불행하게 만들까봐 두려워요
I think you need to think carefully
잘 생각해 보셔야 할 것 같아요
you are hope
당신은 희망입니다
we are here to talk
우리는 얘기하러 여기 있어요
Or should I make a request and take it to the police station to discuss?
아니면 요청해서 경찰서에 가져가서 의논해야 할까요?
Just like these two people
이 두 사람처럼
We want to believe you too
우리도 당신을 믿고 싶어요
but if we could
하지만 우리가 할 수 있다면
Chat with Cong'er in person to confirm.
Cong'er와 직접 채팅하여 확인하세요.
Can save you a lot of unnecessary trouble
불필요한 문제를 많이 줄일 수 있습니다.
I understand, I understand
이해해요, 이해해요
How about I contact her and ask?
내가 그 사람한테 연락해서 물어보는 게 어때?
no problem
괜찮아요
Talk to your child
자녀와 대화하세요
OK
좋아요
Wait a minute, wait a minute, thank you
잠깐만, 잠깐만, 고마워요
Hold on
기다리다
silver
은
What do you want to say to her?
그녀에게 무슨 말을 하고 싶나요?
Do you think she is a robot?
그녀가 로봇이라고 생각하시나요?
I want to ask her some questions
나는 그녀에게 몇 가지 질문을 하고 싶습니다.
test her reaction
그녀의 반응을 테스트해 보세요
What's wrong
뭐가 문제 야
Well, you have to think about it
글쎄, 생각해 봐야 해
Where can I say this?
이 말은 어디서 할 수 있나요?
interrupt me anytime
언제든지 방해해
silver
은
can I ask you some questions?
질문을 좀해도 되겠습니까?
Can we sit down and talk?
우리 앉아서 얘기 좀 할 수 있을까요?
silver
은
After the police rescued you
경찰이 당신을 구출한 후
See mom and dad again
엄마 아빠 다시 만나요
Do you still recognize them?
아직도 그들을 알아볼 수 있나요?
confirm
확인하다
But it's been a long time
하지만 오랜만이야
How are you so sure?
어떻게 그렇게 확신해요?
they are your parents
그 분이 네 부모님이야
By what?
무엇에 의해?
Is it just because of the face?
단지 얼굴 때문일까요?
Don't worry, Conger.
걱정하지 마세요, 콩저.
let's take our time
시간을 좀 가지자
Come and sit down
와서 앉으세요
come over
이리와
Are you OK?
괜찮으세요?
beautiful
아름다운
I have read many reports
나는 많은 보고서를 읽었습니다.
many children missing
많은 아이들이 실종됐다
they will reject their parents
그들은 그들의 부모를 거부할 것이다
treat them like strangers
그들을 낯선 사람처럼 대한다
After all, you were still young then
어차피 그때는 넌 아직 어렸잖아
Experienced a lot again
또 많이 경험했어요
So we forget some people or things
그래서 우리는 사람이나 사물을 잊어버립니다.
This is a normal reaction
이는 정상적인 반응입니다.
I only remember
나만 기억난다
I remember they were my parents
그 분들이 내 부모님이었던 걸로 기억하는데
That's because you planted the original obsession in your heart
그건 니가 마음속에 원초적인 집착을 심었기 때문이야
That's why you believe this unconditionally
그렇기 때문에 무조건 믿으세요.
did not expect
기대하지 않았다
Maybe Android?
아마 안드로이드?
enough
충분한
silver
은
if you don't want to answer
대답하고 싶지 않다면
We cannot be responsible for our biological children
우리는 생물학적 자녀에 대해 책임을 질 수 없습니다.
Will his parents love him more?
그의 부모가 그를 더 사랑할까요?
we are family
우리는 가족
they won't abandon me
그들은 나를 버리지 않을 거야
can you go?
갈 수 있어?
dad
아빠
Are you smoking again?
또 담배 피우세요?
Delicious
맛있는
I won't smoke again
나는 다시는 담배를 피우지 않을 것이다
Two people came to the house today
오늘은 두 사람이 집에 왔습니다
Are they here to arrest Uncle Li Ye?
리예 삼촌을 체포하러 온 걸까요?
Children, don't think blindly.
어린이 여러분, 맹목적으로 생각하지 마십시오.
Uncle Li Ye will be fine
리예 삼촌은 괜찮을 거야
correct
옳은
these two people
이 두 사람
What did I tell you at home?
내가 집에서 뭐라고 말했지?
Did I embarrass you?
내가 당신을 당황하게 만들었나요?
No
아니요
They didn't make things difficult for me
그 사람들은 나를 힘들게 하지 않았어
This is good
이것은 좋다
Huang Shiping’s parents passed away
황시핑 부모님 사망
Li Han’s mother ten years ago
10년 전 리한의 어머니
Hemiplegia caused by cerebral hemorrhage
뇌출혈로 인한 편마비
so her father takes care of her
그래서 그녀의 아버지가 그녀를 돌본다.
So before Huang Konger was seven years old,
그래서 황공거가 7살이 되기 전에,
It is impossible for the elderly on both sides to take care of them
양쪽의 노인들이 그들을 돌보는 것은 불가능합니다
Missing child information released by police
경찰이 공개한 실종아동 정보
There is indeed a person named Huang Conger
황콩거(Huang Conger)라는 사람이 실제로 있다.
The police officer in charge is also named Hu
담당 경찰관의 이름도 Hu입니다.
Do you have other photos?
다른 사진도 있나요?
No
아니요
Lost children pictures
잃어버린 아이들 사진
Parents usually report the crime to the police
부모는 대개 범죄를 경찰에 신고합니다.
But Huang Shipeng said
그러나 Huang Shipeng은 이렇게 말했습니다.
I don’t have Huang Conger at all
황붕어가 전혀 없어요
childhood photos
어린 시절 사진
This could be caused by
이는 다음으로 인해 발생할 수 있습니다.
Is he still wary of us?
그 사람이 아직도 우리를 경계하는 걸까요?
How do you prove that this girl is the one in this photo?
이 사진 속의 소녀가 바로 그 소녀라는 것을 어떻게 증명하나요?
This is Huang Conger
황콩거 입니다
I think three year old girls are the same.
세 살짜리 여자아이들도 마찬가지인 것 같아요.
It's normal if you don't recognize it
인식하지 못하는 것이 정상이다
Conger is now twelve years old
콩저는 이제 열두 살이 되었습니다.
Of course a lot has changed
물론 많이 변했지
Come and watch
와서 시청하세요
sorry
죄송합니다
we have never met this man
우리는 이 사람을 만난 적이 없다
Then let me ask again
그럼 다시 물어볼게요
let me do it
내가 하게 해줘
Wife, take a look
아내, 좀 보세요
Have you met this person?
이 사람을 만나본 적 있나요?
I did not see it
나 못 봤어
I've never seen that before, okay
난 그런 걸 본 적이 없어, 알았어
sorry
죄송합니다
None of us had ever met the family.
우리 중 누구도 그 가족을 만난 적이 없었습니다.
beautiful
아름다운
OK
좋아요
silver
은
Gentlemen
신사
Look at the robot with your bright eyes
밝은 눈으로 로봇을 보세요
What does this have to do with my daughter?
이것이 내 딸과 무슨 관련이 있나요?
beautiful
아름다운
Then please come back, please come back
그럼 돌아와주세요, 돌아와주세요
It's clear now
이제 분명해졌어
Huang Shiping and his wife due to physical reasons
황십핑(Huang Shiping)과 그의 아내가 신체적 이유로
She can't give birth to a child
그 사람은 아이를 낳을 수가 없어요.
After buying android
안드로이드 구매 후
It was stolen again and made the news.
또 도난당해 화제가 됐습니다.
Huang Conger’s name and experience
황붕어의 이름과 경력
Is it necessary to go to such trouble?
그런 문제를 겪을 필요가 있습니까?
Why use Cong'er?
왜 Cong'er를 사용하나요?
Because of the same surname
같은 성 때문에
Age is also constant
나이도 일정하다.
More convenient to operate
작동이 더욱 편리해졌습니다.
Huang Shipeng is full of lies
Huang Shipeng은 거짓말로 가득 차 있습니다.
Maybe it has something to do with Li Yi
아마도 Li Yi와 관련이 있을 것입니다.
He is also lying to us
그 사람은 우리에게도 거짓말을 하고 있어요
It seems that I don't want to force him.
강요하고 싶지 않은 것 같습니다.
He won't tell the truth
그 사람은 진실을 말하지 않을 거야
what are you going to do
당신은 무엇을 할 예정입니까?
News on this site
이 사이트의 뉴스
An identification incident recently occurred at Mingmu Gene Research Institute
최근 명무유전자연구소에서 신원확인 사건이 발생했습니다.
a man who looks like a robot
로봇처럼 생긴 남자
Due to adverse reactions after injection of ID drugs
ID약물 주사 후 이상반응으로 인해
It is reported that the man’s family has filed a lawsuit against Mingmo
남성 가족이 밍모를 상대로 소송을 제기한 것으로 알려졌다.
Dedicated to bright eyes
밝은 눈을 위한 헌신
Correct the investigation and handling links and strengthen supervision.
조사 및 처리 연계를 바로잡고 감독을 강화한다.
Zhao Yuan
조 위안
Do you know where Qingnu went?
Qingnu가 어디로 갔는지 아십니까?
Cheng Nu
쳉 누
I just saw him applying to medicine.
방금 그가 의학에 지원하는 것을 봤어요.
Apply for medicine
약을 신청하세요
Is Qingnu here to get the potion?
Qingnu가 물약을 얻으러 여기에 있습니까?
Yes
예
Doesn’t it require two people to sign?
서명하려면 두 사람이 필요하지 않나요?
Isn't this what you signed up for?
이거 가입한 거 아냐?
Mr. Huang
황 씨
Where is Conger?
콩거는 어디에 있나요?
at home
집에서
What's wrong
뭐가 문제 야
What's your job
당신의 직업은 무엇입니까
silver
은
Go away, Conger, go away
저리 가세요 콩저 저리 가세요
What's your job
당신의 직업은 무엇입니까
silver
은
Qingnuo go away
칭누오 가세요
Cheng Nu
쳉 누
what are you going to do
당신은 무엇을 할 예정입니까?
He insists Conger is a robot
그는 콩거가 로봇이라고 주장한다
What medicine should I give her?
그녀에게 어떤 약을 주어야 할까요?
You won't cooperate, will you?
당신은 협조하지 않을 거에요, 그렇죠?
leave my house immediately
당장 내 집에서 나가
Otherwise I will call the police
안 그러면 경찰에 신고할 거예요
Call the police
경찰에 전화하세요
Well, report it
응 신고해
pay it forward
앞으로 지불
Cheng Nu
쳉 누
Have you had enough trouble?
충분히 고생하셨나요?
You don't have my signature authority
당신은 내 서명 권한이 없습니다
you know you might encounter
당신은 당신이 만날 수 있다는 것을 알고 있습니다
What are the consequences?
그 결과는 무엇입니까?
please leave
떠나주세요
Then I'll leave first
그럼 나 먼저 갈게
Hold on
기다리다
Can I chat with you privately?
개인적으로 대화를 나눌 수 있나요?
Why did you use my signature?
내 서명을 사용한 이유는 무엇입니까?
the last words you said
네가 마지막으로 한 말
From a researcher's perspective
연구자의 관점에서
I'm speaking from Cong'er's perspective.
나는 Cong'er의 관점에서 말하고 있습니다.
Is it important?
그것은 중요한가?
Huang Shiping hopes we can do this
Huang Shiping은 우리가 이것을 할 수 있기를 바랍니다
Don't bother them anymore
더 이상 그들을 괴롭히지 마세요
So he said something about Li Yi
그래서 그는 Li Yi에 대해 뭔가를 말했습니다.
and
그리고
let's talk and see
얘기하고 보자
Huang Shipeng was owed transportation expenses before
Huang Shipeng은 이전에 교통비를 지불해야했습니다.
when he goes to collect debt
그가 빚을 받으러 갔을 때
He was even beaten
심지어 구타까지 당했다
Li Yi later discovered this
Li Yi는 나중에 이것을 발견했습니다.
He came forward to help Huang Shipeng
그는 Huang Shipeng을 돕기 위해 나섰습니다.
I got all my money back
돈 다 돌려받았어
since then
그때부터
Huang Shipeng has always been thinking about Li Yi
Huang Shipeng은 항상 Li Yi에 대해 생각하고 있습니다.
treated like family
가족처럼 대함
I really thought about it
정말 생각해봤는데
I wanna go
나는 가고 싶다
Yes, Brother Peng
네, 펑 형제님
Brother, let me ask you something
형님, 뭐 하나 물어볼게요
Did you encounter any difficulties?
어려움을 겪었나요?
If you have any difficulties please let me know
어려운 점이 있으면 알려주세요.
I can help, I will help
내가 도와줄게, 내가 도와줄게
Brother Peng
펭 형제
I didn't mean not to say that.
그런 말을 하지 않으려는 건 아니었어요.
I am anxious
나는 불안하다
will cause you trouble
당신에게 문제를 일으킬 것입니다
No. What's the problem?
아니요. 문제가 무엇인가요?
I can help, I will help
내가 도와줄게, 내가 도와줄게
Don't worry
괜찮아요
I'll solve it myself
내가 직접 해결해볼게요
He said he always felt
늘 느꼈다고 하더군요
What is hidden in Li Yi's heart?
리이의 마음속에는 무엇이 숨겨져 있을까?
he will eventually leave
그는 결국 떠날 것이다
So when we first went looking for it
그래서 처음 찾으러 갔을 때
He is afraid that we will bring trouble to Li Yi
그는 우리가 Li Yi에게 문제를 가져올까봐 두려워합니다.
That's why I'm hiding this
그래서 이걸 숨기고 있는 거야
Does he know the whereabouts of Li Yi?
그는 Li Yi의 행방을 알고 있나요?
But Huang Shipeng said
그러나 Huang Shipeng은 이렇게 말했습니다.
He often comes to visit them
그는 그들을 자주 방문한다
I just came here a few days ago
저는 며칠 전에 여기 왔었어요.
So I think
그래서 나는 생각한다
We'll just wait here obediently
우리는 순순히 여기서 기다리겠습니다
Maybe Li Yi himself will show up.
어쩌면 리이 자신도 나타날지도 모른다.
I know
알아요
Know if you are in trouble
당신이 곤경에 처해 있는지 알아보세요.
Do you want to speak on behalf of the Huang family?
황 가족을 대표하여 말씀하시겠습니까?
Once you do this
일단 이렇게 하면
In order to protect his daughter Huang Shiping
딸 황시핑(Huang Shiping)을 보호하기 위해
I will tell you what I have hidden in my heart.
내 마음 속에 숨겨둔 것을 알려 드리겠습니다.
After all, my daughter is much more important than Li Yi
결국 내 딸은 Li Yi보다 훨씬 더 중요합니다
you make a fuss
당신은 소란을 피우다
Just to check on myself
그냥 나 자신을 확인하기 위해
of course not
당연히 아니지
I won't make a deal with Huang Shipeng
나는 황십펑(Huang Shipeng)과 거래하지 않을 것이다
About Huang Conger
황콩거 소개
I also want to check
나도 확인하고 싶어
So you took advantage of me
그래서 당신은 나를 이용했어요
everyone benefits
모두가 혜택을 받습니다
I really don't want to fight
난 정말 싸우고 싶지 않아
You are really hopeless
넌 정말 절망적이야
good night, see you tomorrow
잘자 내일 봐
This person today
오늘 이 사람
Did she ask you for money again?
그 사람이 또 돈 달라고 했어?
correct
옳은
my heart is always troubled
내 마음은 항상 불안해요
I said what we said this afternoon
오늘 오후에 우리가 한 말을 내가 말했어
Can you fool them?
당신은 그들을 속일 수 있습니까?
The bright eyes won't bother us Conger then, right?
그러면 그 밝은 눈은 우리를 괴롭히지 않을 것입니다. 붕장어, 그렇죠?
The baby may not be asleep yet
아기가 아직 잠들지 않았을 수도 있어요
don't let her hear
그녀가 듣지 못하게 해라
why do not you answer the call?
왜 전화를 안 받아?
This is Huang Shipeng’s bank statement
이것은 Huang Shipeng의 은행 명세서입니다.
a month ago
한 달 전
he withdrew a large amount of money
그는 많은 돈을 인출했다
Until Li Yigang resigned
리이강이 사임할 때까지
I got it back yesterday
어제 돌려받았어요
I checked with their company
그 회사에 확인해 봤는데
Profits are always slim
이익은 항상 적다
You can't make much money in a year
1년 안에 돈을 많이 벌 수는 없다.
Every time I deposit it into my account, I withdraw it all.
내 계좌에 입금할 때마다 모두 인출됩니다.
He withdrew a lot of money
그는 많은 돈을 인출했다
What is it used for?
그것은 무엇을 위해 사용됩니까?
still angry
여전히 화나있어
I admit
나는 인정한다
I have a question today
오늘은 질문이 있어요
but i also have to
하지만 나도 그래야 해
Let him tell you about Li Yi
그에게 Li Yi에 대해 말하게 해주세요
That's why I deliberately made him angry
그래서 일부러 화나게 만든 거야
Who do you know?
당신은 누구를 알고 있나요?
he didn't say anything
그는 아무 말도 하지 않았어요
It's family now
이제 가족이에요
They all resist me
그들은 모두 나에게 저항한다
so i was thinking
그래서 내가 생각하고 있었어
Do we want to be alone?
우리는 혼자 있고 싶나요?
Let's talk to Cong'er
콩어에게 말을 걸어보자
I think I'm smart
내 생각엔 내가 똑똑한 것 같아
It must have a lot to do with Li Yi
리이와 관련이 많겠군요
How about you help me one more time?
한 번 더 도와주시는 게 어때요?
You just feel like you’re not wrong, right?
당신은 단지 당신이 틀리지 않은 것 같은 느낌이 들죠?
Just because I'm valuable
단지 내가 소중한 사람이니까
Come and apologize to me
와서 나한테 사과해
And three more favorite drinks
그리고 좋아하는 음료 세 가지 더
I punished myself three times today
오늘 나 자신에게 세 번 벌을 내렸다
all
모두
you don't have to punish yourself
당신은 자신을 처벌할 필요가 없습니다
If you can drink better than me
나보다 술을 잘 마실 수 있다면
i assure you
나는 당신에게 확신합니다
Go talk to Cong'er
가서 Cong'er와 대화해 보세요
OK
좋아요
give up
포기하다
Do you know why you lost?
왜 졌는지 아세요?
If you lose, you lose.
잃으면 지는 것이다.
No reason
이유없이
We competed over who could drink the most.
우리는 누가 가장 많이 마실 수 있는지 경쟁했습니다.
Not like anyone drinks fast
누구처럼 술을 빨리 마시지 않아
Of course you will get drunk if you drink too much
물론 술을 많이 마시면 ​​취하게 된다.
Even after drinking, she still cares so much
술을 마셔도 여전히 신경쓰이는 그녀
you are always like this
너는 항상 이렇다
To win, to achieve goals
승리하기 위해, 목표를 달성하기 위해
No matter what, just move forward
무슨 일이 있어도 앞으로 나아가면 돼
But you can only see now
하지만 이제야 볼 수 있지
Can't pay attention to details at all
세부 사항에 전혀 주의를 기울이지 못함
you are like this
당신은 이렇습니다
In the end, it’s only you who gets hurt
결국 상처받는 건 너뿐이야
ok i lost
알았어 내가 졌어
I lose, okay?
내가 졌어, 알았지?
you can't always control yourself
당신은 항상 자신을 통제할 수 없습니다
correct
옳은
always you
언제나 당신
i have been working
나는 계속 일하고있어
Never give yourself a break
절대 쉬지 마세요.
correct
옳은
Yes
예
You also know you are annoying
너도 짜증나는거 알지?
correct
옳은
sorry
죄송합니다
look
바라보다
that's what i mean
그게 내 말이에요
Thanks
감사해요
if not you
당신이 아니라면
Robot found in shanty town
판자촌에서 발견된 로봇
Maybe I can't find it now
지금은 못 찾을 수도 있겠네요
my mother's thoughts
우리 엄마의 생각
So what are the plans for the future?
그렇다면 앞으로의 계획은 무엇입니까?
Stop hiding it from me
나한테는 그만 숨기자
I'm your partner
나는 당신의 파트너입니다
You don't need to push me away
나를 밀어낼 필요는 없어
moray eel side
곰치 쪽
I'll find a chance to talk to her again
나는 그녀와 다시 이야기할 기회를 찾을 것이다
But that's not the case now
하지만 지금은 그렇지 않아요
This time we tried harder.
이번에는 더 열심히 노력했습니다.
OK
좋아요
It seems we have nothing but work
우리에겐 일밖에 없는 것 같아
she didn't talk about anything else
그 사람은 다른 얘기는 안 했어
you
너
You first
당신이 먼저
Don't comment on me anymore
더 이상 나에 대해 댓글을 달지 마세요
how did you find me?
나를 어떻게 찾았어요?
Shen told me
쉔이 나한테 말했어
You often drink here
여기서 술을 자주 마시잖아
can I ask you something
뭐 좀 물어봐도 될까요?
that shantytown
그 판자촌
I can't find it online
온라인에서 찾을 수 없어요
Any information about android
안드로이드에 관한 모든 정보
There
거기
what happened?
무슨 일이에요?
concrete
구체적인
I am also not certain
나 역시 확실하지 않다.
I heard the shed renovation project has been going on for a long time.
창고 개조 프로젝트가 오랫동안 진행되고 있다고 들었습니다.
But it's not going well
그런데 잘 안 되네
It's deserted there
거기는 황폐해
Jurisdiction unclear
관할권이 불분명함
Is this why Lu Yan is hiding there?
이것이 Lu Yan이 거기 숨어 있는 이유인가요?
What's wrong
뭐가 문제 야
there is nothing
아무것도 없다